http://www.glockstore.com/privacy-policy

WE ARE SLOWLY CATCHING UP, BUT ARE CURRENTLY SHIPPING NON-FIREARM, IN STOCK ORDERS PLACED ON:New ProductsOver $100 Ships Free30-Day GuaranteeTopshot TuesdayTrainingFree CatalogNew ProductsOver $100 Ships FreeOver $100 Ships Free30-Day GuaranteeTopshot TuesdayTrainingFree CatalogNew ProductsAbout UsStore LocationCareersShipping and returnsPrivacy PolicyContact UsRequest CatalogPrivacy Policy OverviewGS Performance, LLC is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to our website at GlockStore.com. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us.By registering or placing an order on this website, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy.Information we collect from you:When you visit, register, or order products or services you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name, contact details and credit or debit card information. We may also collect information about your usage of our website as well as information about you from messages you post to the website and e-mails or letters you send to us.To maintain customer service standards and to assist staff training, we may also record and monitor incoming calls.Use of your information:Your information will enable us to provide you with access to all parts of our website and to supply the goods or services you have requested. It will also enable us to bill you and to contact you, when necessary, concerning your orders. We will also use and analyze the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business.In particular, we may use your information to contact you for your views on our services and to occasionally notify you about important changes or developments to the website or our services. Further, where you have consented, we might also use your information to let you know by email about other products and services which we offer, which may be of interest to you. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know.Disclosure of your information:Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent.Cookies:Cookies are small amounts of information which we may store on your computer.Unless you have indicated your objection, when disclosing your details to us, our system will issue cookies to your computer when you log on to the site. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and to personalize the content of the site for you. You may set up your computer to reject cookies by following the relevant instructions which can be found at www.aboutcookies.org. In that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our site. If you do not wish to receive cookies in the future, please let us know.Security and Retention:We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorized persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.Accessing and Updating:You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please login to your account to modify your details. You can also contact us at info@glockstore.comChanges to our Privacy PolicyAny future changes to our privacy policy will be posted to the website and, when appropriate, through e-mail notification.ContactAll comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to:GlockStore4770 Ruffner StreetSan Diego CA 92111(800) 601-8273info@glockstore.com
